TREVOR BENAVIDES

C: (303) 829-9013 1884 Mountain Sage Run, Littleton, CO 80126 gratefultrev@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Varied set of skills including; Software development, social media marketing, hardware repairs/upgrades to apple products and general technology. I have exquisite communication/conflict resolution skills and am highly adaptable.

I am a semi-professional photographer with a diverse portfolio including content creation for web pages/social media outlets. Macro photography of insects and small products. Concert photos, portraits, assorted product/art photos and storefront photos.

Experience being a brand

WORK HISTORY

Independent Brand Ambassador • Madera Outdoor

- May 2017 to Current
 - Madera Outdoor brand ambassador handling social media marketing photography.

ambassador.

Event Manager • Spectra Art Space

Denver, CO • August 2016 to September 2017

- Event Booking, products photos, promotion, production. including setup of lighting and stage).
- Retail sales Product photography.

Social Media Management • Water Pulse

- March 2015 to March 2016
 - Part of the R&D Team; Networking at events to promote the products.
 - Product education at trade shows and events.

Independent Contractor • Precision Windows and Siding

- September 2015 to February 2016
 - Door to door sales, including personalized sales pitch.
 - Commissions based on window and siding sales.

EDUCATION

Currently Attending - Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp • *University of Denver*

Denver, CO • 2018

Currently Attending - Full Stack Web Development Program • *Free Code Camp*

Online • 2018

Currently Attending - Apple Software Development • *Apple Swift Playgrounds*Online • 2018